<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on David Hinojosa</title><link>https://davhinojosa.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on David Hinojosa</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, David Hinojosa Gonzalez.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:01:02 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://davhinojosa.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Coolify Changed My Life and Allowed Me to Ship Faster</title><link>https://davhinojosa.com/2024/07/12/how-coolify-changed-my-life-and-allowed-me-to-ship-faster/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:01:02 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://davhinojosa.com/2024/07/12/how-coolify-changed-my-life-and-allowed-me-to-ship-faster/</guid><description>Ever since I first learned about containers in Django For Professionals, I&amp;rsquo;ve added container orchestration with Docker Compose on all my projects. Even my teammates jokingly started calling me &amp;ldquo;Docker Commander&amp;rdquo;. The thing was, I made them for dev first environments, worrying about deploying them on platforms like fly.io or Google Cloud Run later. This worked for a while, but could not be sustainable. Reading about the Vercel situation got me thinking I should consider self-hosted alternatives to avoid being vendor locked in and making shipping faster and easier.</description></item><item><title>TIL: Git Pre-Commits</title><link>https://davhinojosa.com/til/pre-commit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:00:46 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://davhinojosa.com/til/pre-commit/</guid><description>As I was configuring the deployment of this blog, I wanted to see how I could automate the build and publish process. I knew using Github Actions was a common approach. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I envisioned in my head:
Implementing this approach caused me a bit of trouble with managing the public folder&amp;rsquo;s Git history and was a headache to get working properly. Best to toss it and start over again. Enter Git Hooks.</description></item></channel></rss>